Guide to the National Education Association-Committees records, 1857-1996 NEA1003.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Education and Library Networks Coalition, 1994-2001; Series 29
  - EdLiNC Kits, 1998; Series 29 (Box 4798, Folder 2)
  - Education and Library Coalition, 1996; Series 29 (Box 4798, Folder 3)
  - Education and Library Networks Coalition (EdLiNC), 1996-1998; Series 29 (Box 4798, Folder 4)
  - E-Rate 1999-2000 [1/2], Series 29 (Box 4798, Folder 5)
  - E-Rate 1999-2000 [2/2], Series 29 (Box 4798, Folder 6)
  - E-Rate 2001 [1/3], Series 29 (Box 4799, Folder 1)
  - E-Rate 2001 [1/3], Series 29 (Box 4799, Folder 2)
  - E-Rate 2001 [1/3], Series 29 (Box 4799, Folder 3)
  - Speeches 1998, Series 29 (Box 4799, Folder 4)
  - State EdLiNCs, 1997; Series 29 (Box 4799, Folder 5)